downeu.net 2012-09-20

# Privacy

Our privacy principles were changed.We’ll never sell your personal information or share it.Other than rare circumstances like valid legal requests.

We don't accept erotic,sexual,pornographic contents to our website.We are working find inappropriate content.Please report sexual,erotic,porno or any harmful content via comments and you can send email to downeu[at]gmail.com about this issues. **  
**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Downeu.net. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

 **Downeu.net** is committed to protecting your privacy. Downeu.net does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. Downeu.net will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.

 **Third Party Advertising**  
We use search software third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. _This ads only a link and was added to posts and search pages._

 **Third Party Cookies**  
 **We do not use any advertising that require cookies at this time.**

 **Modification of Privacy Policy**  
Downeu.net reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update the Privacy Policy and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.

 **Use of Information**  
Downeu.net will not reveal any personal information that users provide to us to any third party without their permission. Downeu.net uses users’ IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. This information does not contain anything that can identify users personally.

Although Downeu.net does not specifically seek to obtain any information from minors, this website is open to all. We urge children to use our website only after they have discussed it with their parents.

Downeu.net generates search results automatically from databases and any search may return unexpected or unwanted references. These references may contain offensive, obscene, or illegal material. Because Downeu.net merely links to and does not publish content supplied by third parties or which is generally available on the Internet. Please use this site and any material referred on it responsibly.

Sometimes some contributors wanted article posting in our website and we accept these requests for more quality web,also we acts selectively about contributors. **We dont have any bad bots disturbing to websites.We dont want lock contents.  
**
